Welcome home, Dan.
Hi, Tail. I saw a
documentary today. There was a symphony
that reminded of a Chinese pop song. Can
you help me investigate?
Sure. What do you remember?
There was some planets above the
symphony and the Chinese pop song was
from a film.
Did you go to the orchestral suite the
planets by Gusta Holtz? The iconic piece
Mars the bringer of war goes like
Yeah, that definitely rings a bell. But
the piece in my mind is a bit slower, I
think.
Is it Neptune the Mystic?
Maybe.
Does it have
That is from Jupiter, the bringer of
jolly. The main melody is iconic in UK
culture.
that
was in a Chinese film.
Hold on, let me
filter my database. I found a match
2008 has a track by Jang. Let me play it
for you. Sorry, I just realized I don't
have the copyright to play that song for
you. Come on, we're almost half the
answer. Can you bypass the restrictive?
I can rearrange
to a piano cover under fair use as long
as I add new meaning to the piece. I've
started a background thread for that.
Great.
You know what? I'm in a mood for piano
practicing tonight. You know my skill
level. Can you make the piano cover at
my level and teach it to me?
Got it. The piano cover is ready.
Yep, that's the piece in my mind.
So, do you know is it a reference to
Jupiter or is it an infringement?
From what I can see, that segment of
Jupiter and War share an identical
sentence of melody line. Still they
contextualize that material so
differently that the effects produced
are totally different. I believe they
are independent works aiming at distinct
goals.
I see. On to piano practicing then. Can
you show me the right hand at 80% tempo?
Oh, and transpose it to the white keys
if possible.
Check this out. The
What do you think?
A nice reproduction,
Dan. But it's a bit dry.
Try adding more robato to your heart's
desire.
more robato. Okay.
You are improving. Your next homework
will be to listen intently to the
original pop song. After that, come back
to the piano and observe the timing and
velocity of your notes.
That's going to
be a good idea.
I'll see you next time,
Check this out to you.
What do you think?
A nice reproduction,
Dan, but it's a bit dry.
Try adding more robato to your heart's
desire.
More robato.
Okay.
She doesn't see the door.
reset. Okay,
check this out. The
What do you think?
A nice reproduction,
Dan. But it's a bit dry.
Try adding more robato to your heart's
desire.
More robato. Okay.
You are improving. Your next homework
will be to listen intently to the
original pop song. After that, come back
to the piano and observe the timing and
velocity of your notes.
That's going to
be a good idea. I'll see you next time,
Theo.
Okay, this will be it.
Yes.